College of Engineering and Applied Sciences Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Administrative Records, 2000-2015; nam_ua670-2; 15 cubic ft.
  - Information Studies Ph.D. Program, Undated; nam_ua670-2_298 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Information Studies Provosts Advisory Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_299 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Information Studies School Library Media, Undated; nam_ua670-2_300 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Information Studies Provosts Advisory Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_301 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Information Studies -Course Action, Undated; nam_ua670-2_302 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Infrasim, Undated; nam_ua670-2_303 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Infrasim Resources, Undated; nam_ua670-2_304 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Infrasim - Simulation Day, 2002 October; nam_ua670-2_305 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - International Sematech, Undated; nam_ua670-2_306 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Intiatives for Women (IFW), ca. 1998; nam_ua670-2_307 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - International, Undated; nam_ua670-2_308 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - International Education Appointee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_309 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Student Profiles, Undated; nam_ua670-2_310 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Ankara University, Undated; nam_ua670-2_311 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Delegation, Undated; nam_ua670-2_312 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - International Education Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_313 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - IST, Undated; nam_ua670-2_314 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - IST Accreditation, Undated; nam_ua670-2_315 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - IST Course Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_316 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - IST General Information, Undated; nam_ua670-2_317 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - IST Hiring Plans, Undated; nam_ua670-2_318 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - IST Internship, Undated; nam_ua670-2_319 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - IST423 (temp until 01/2007), 2007 January; nam_ua670-2_320 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - IT/CCI Task force, Undated; nam_ua670-2_321 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - IT Commons, Undated; nam_ua670-2_322 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - IT Commons, 2004-2005; nam_ua670-2_323 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - ITC Academics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_324 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - IT Commons Background, Undated; nam_ua670-2_325 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - IT Commons Committee Resources, Undated; nam_ua670-2_326 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - IT Commons Course Catalog, Undated; nam_ua670-2_327 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - IT Commons Development, Undated; nam_ua670-2_328 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - IT Commons External Constituents for Development, Undated; nam_ua670-2_329 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - IT Commons Faculty, Undated; nam_ua670-2_330 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - IT Commons Faculty RPF, Undated; nam_ua670-2_331 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - IT Commons Handouts, Undated; nam_ua670-2_332 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - ITC Hires, Undated; nam_ua670-2_333 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - IT Commons Management Group, Undated; nam_ua670-2_334 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - IT Commons MOU - Computer Science, Undated; nam_ua670-2_335 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - IT Commons Personnel Art/Music, Undated; nam_ua670-2_336 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - IT Commons Personnel Computer Science, Undated; nam_ua670-2_337 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - IT Commons Personnel Criminal Justice, Undated; nam_ua670-2_338 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - IT Commons Personnel Economics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_339 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - IT Commons Personnel ETAP, Undated; nam_ua670-2_340 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - IT Commons Personnel Geography and Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_341 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - IT Commons Personnel Information Science, Undated; nam_ua670-2_342 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - IT Commons Personnel Physics/Biology, Undated; nam_ua670-2_343 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - IT Commons Personnel Political Science, Undated; nam_ua670-2_344 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - IT Commons Personnel Public Administration, Undated; nam_ua670-2_345 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - IT Commons Pictures, Undated; nam_ua670-2_346 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - IT Commons Searches, Undated; nam_ua670-2_347 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - IT Commons Steering Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_348 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - IT Commons Survey, Undated; nam_ua670-2_349 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - IT Commons Three-Ring, Undated; nam_ua670-2_350 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - IT Commons UPC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_351 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - IT Learning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_352 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - IT Commons Search, Undated; nam_ua670-2_353 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - ITC Course Catalog, Undated; nam_ua670-2_354 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - ITC Faculty Recruit, Undated; nam_ua670-2_355 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - IT Dean Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_356 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - IT Services, Undated; nam_ua670-2_357 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - IT Workforce, Undated; nam_ua670-2_358 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - IT Dean Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_359 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - IT Services, Undated; nam_ua670-2_360 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - IFMR Active, Undated; nam_ua670-2_361 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - IMFR, 2009; nam_ua670-2_362 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Jones Trinity Alliance, 2010-2013; nam_ua670-2_363 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Judaic Studies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_364 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Junior First League LEGO, Undated; nam_ua670-2_365 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Kaplan Foundations Sheila Kaplan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_366 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - LAAP, Undated; nam_ua670-2_367 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Legal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_368 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Initiative, Undated; nam_ua670-2_369 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Steven Levy, 2012; nam_ua670-2_370 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Librarianship (Excellence), Undated; nam_ua670-2_371 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Library Programs Symposium, 2014 October 9; nam_ua670-2_372 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Library Renovation, Undated; nam_ua670-2_373 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Library University Libraries Newsletter, Undated; nam_ua670-2_374 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Making It Real Part II, Undated; nam_ua670-2_375 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Massoni, Al, Undated; nam_ua670-2_376 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Mission Review II, Undated; nam_ua670-2_377 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Mementos, Undated; nam_ua670-2_378 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - MOUs, Undated; nam_ua670-2_379 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Navitas, Undated; nam_ua670-2_380 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NCWIT, Undated; nam_ua670-2_381 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - NERFI, Undated; nam_ua670-2_382 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - NERFI Joint Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_383 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New College, Undated; nam_ua670-2_384 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New College Joan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_385 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - New College Resolution, Undated; nam_ua670-2_386 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - New File-Health IT, Undated; nam_ua670-2_387 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - News Letter, Undated; nam_ua670-2_388 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Newit Scorecard, Undated; nam_ua670-2_389 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - New York State Central Accounting System Need Analysis, Undated; nam_ua670-2_390 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NIJ Elect Crimes Partnership, Undated; nam_ua670-2_391 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NSA CAE/IAE, Undated; nam_ua670-2_392 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NSF CPATH Proposal, 2009; nam_ua670-2_393 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NSF Day, 2011; nam_ua670-2_394 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - NSF ISCC Workshop, Undated; nam_ua670-2_395 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - NSF ITR Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_396 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - NSF Scholarships for Service 2001 Proposal, nam_ua670-2_397 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - NSF SFS Copies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_398 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NSF SFS Grant, Undated; nam_ua670-2_399 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - NTCIR, 2012; nam_ua670-2_400 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - NTCIR, 2009; nam_ua670-2_401 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - NTCIR conference, 2006; nam_ua670-2_402 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - NTIR New Trends in Informatics Research Conference, Undated; nam_ua670-2_403 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - NYS Cyber Security Conference, Undated; nam_ua670-2_404 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - NYSERnet, Undated; nam_ua670-2_405 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - NYSL New York State Library, Undated; nam_ua670-2_406 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - NYS Public Sector Academy, Undated; nam_ua670-2_407 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - NYSTAR, Undated; nam_ua670-2_408 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - NYSTAR Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_409 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - NYS OFT/CIO Workforce, Undated; nam_ua670-2_410 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - NYS Writer's Institute, Undated; nam_ua670-2_411 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - NY CIO Academy Advisory Board, Undated; nam_ua670-2_412 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - NYCWIT, 2013; nam_ua670-2_413 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - NY CIO Academy, Undated; nam_ua670-2_414 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - NY CIO Academy Advisory Board, Undated; nam_ua670-2_415 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - NY Opportunity Online Broadband Summit, Undated; nam_ua670-2_416 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - NY Wired for Education, Undated; nam_ua670-2_417 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - NYLA, Undated; nam_ua670-2_418 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - NYLA Online Course, 2012 Spring; nam_ua670-2_419 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - NYPTI, Undated; nam_ua670-2_420 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - NYS Broadband Council, Undated; nam_ua670-2_421 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - NYS DOH - Ozlem Uzuner/Jim Dias, Undated; nam_ua670-2_422 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - NYS Forum, Undated; nam_ua670-2_423 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NYS Grid, Undated; nam_ua670-2_424 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NYSUNY 2020, Undated; nam_ua670-2_425 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NYS IT Workforce, Undated; nam_ua670-2_426 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NYSP & OFT Support, Undated; nam_ua670-2_427 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Moving Notes, Undated; nam_ua670-2_428 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ODK, Undated; nam_ua670-2_429 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Office of International Education, Undated; nam_ua670-2_430 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - OLeary Professorship, Undated; nam_ua670-2_431 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Online Teaching & Learning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_432 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Online Learning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_433 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Open Source Festival, Undated; nam_ua670-2_434 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lego, Undated; nam_ua670-2_435 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lego, Undated; nam_ua670-2_436 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - PEAC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_437 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - PEAC-E, Undated; nam_ua670-2_438 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Performance Dashboard, Undated; nam_ua670-2_439 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - PFI, Undated; nam_ua670-2_440 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - PhD Student, Undated; nam_ua670-2_441 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Philips Sue, Undated; nam_ua670-2_442 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Policy Lunch, Undated; nam_ua670-2_443 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Pre-Proposal Purdue, Undated; nam_ua670-2_444 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Presentations DGI, 2000 June 7; nam_ua670-2_445 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Presentations - ITC External, Undated; nam_ua670-2_446 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Presentations President Ryan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_447 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - President Hall, Undated; nam_ua670-2_448 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - President Hall Meeting, Undated; nam_ua670-2_449 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - President Jones (Robert), Undated; nam_ua670-2_450 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Planning for meeting, Undated; nam_ua670-2_451 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - President Jones Inauguration, 2013; nam_ua670-2_452 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Tutu Sisters, Undated; nam_ua670-2_453 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - President Jones UAlbany Vision, Undated; nam_ua670-2_454 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Proposal DOL, Undated; nam_ua670-2_455 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Proposal IGERT Pre-Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_456 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Props, Undated; nam_ua670-2_457 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Provost, Undated; nam_ua670-2_458 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Provosts Assessment Symposium, 2013; nam_ua670-2_459 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Provost's Executive Advisory Council, Undated; nam_ua670-2_460 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Provost Advisory Report, Undated; nam_ua670-2_461 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Public Relations, Undated; nam_ua670-2_462 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Public Security Certificate, Undated; nam_ua670-2_463 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Purdue - CERIAS Affiliation, Undated; nam_ua670-2_464 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Purdue - CERIAS - LAAP, Undated; nam_ua670-2_465 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Recommendation Letters, Undated; nam_ua670-2_466 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Research Benchmark, Undated; nam_ua670-2_467 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Research-Hot Topics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_468 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Research, Office for, Undated; nam_ua670-2_469 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Research Reports, 2011-2012; 2012-2013; 2013-2014; nam_ua670-2_470 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - RPI-Proposal for Regional Node Porgram (1-Corps Node), Undated; nam_ua670-2_471 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Rockefeller College, Undated; nam_ua670-2_472 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Rockefeller College Dean Search, Undated; nam_ua670-2_473 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Rules and Regulations Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_474 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Salient, Undated; nam_ua670-2_475 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - SCLA, Undated; nam_ua670-2_476 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - School of Public Health, Undated; nam_ua670-2_477 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Security Dynamics Network, Undated; nam_ua670-2_478 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SEC-Consolidated Audit Trail, Undated; nam_ua670-2_479 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Selective Investment, 2006-2007; nam_ua670-2_480 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - SEMATECH project, Undated; nam_ua670-2_481 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Seven to Al Mussoni, Undated; nam_ua670-2_482 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SIRF, Undated; nam_ua670-2_483 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SISP, Undated; nam_ua670-2_484 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - smAlbany, 2013; nam_ua670-2_485 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Social Robotics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_486 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Software Alliance Troy, Undated; nam_ua670-2_487 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Space, 2014; nam_ua670-2_488 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Space CCI Student CTR, Undated; nam_ua670-2_489 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Space Issues, Undated; nam_ua670-2_490 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Space Needs, Undated; nam_ua670-2_491 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Space Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_492 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Space Requests-INF, Undated; nam_ua670-2_493 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - SPWG Strategic Planning Working Group, Undated; nam_ua670-2_494 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Staff Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_495 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Stallman, Richard, Undated; nam_ua670-2_496 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Statistics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_497 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - STRAP Proposal ESDC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_498 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Strategic Planning Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_499 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Strategic Plan-It, Undated; nam_ua670-2_500 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Student Actions, Undated; nam_ua670-2_501 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Student Center, Undated; nam_ua670-2_502 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Student Evaluations, Undated; nam_ua670-2_503 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Summer Retreat, Undated; nam_ua670-2_504 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Student Success, Undated; nam_ua670-2_505 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Social Welfare, Undated; nam_ua670-2_506 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - SS, Undated; nam_ua670-2_507 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - SQL Saturday, 2015 July 25; nam_ua670-2_508 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Summer Sessions, Undated; nam_ua670-2_509 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - SunGard Colleges Report, Undated; nam_ua670-2_510 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - SUNY-Business & Education Leadership, Undated; nam_ua670-2_511 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - SUNY Central, Undated; nam_ua670-2_512 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - SUNY- Central Cyber Security, Undated; nam_ua670-2_513 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - SUNY Empire Innovation Program, Undated; nam_ua670-2_514 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - SUNY High Needs, Undated; nam_ua670-2_515 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - SUNY International, Undated; nam_ua670-2_516 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - SUNY Korea, Undated; nam_ua670-2_517 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - SUNY Leadership Conference, Undated; nam_ua670-2_518 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - SUNY Learning Network, Undated; nam_ua670-2_519 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - SWIFT, Undated; nam_ua670-2_520 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Teachapalooza, 2012; nam_ua670-2_521 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Techapalooza, Undated; nam_ua670-2_522 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Tech Valley Code Camp, Undated; nam_ua670-2_523 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Tech Valley High School, Undated; nam_ua670-2_524 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - TechConnex, Undated; nam_ua670-2_525 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Technology Needs, Undated; nam_ua670-2_526 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - TERA Grid Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_527 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - TVHS Project, Undated; nam_ua670-2_528 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - UAlbany Day, 2009; nam_ua670-2_529 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - UAlbany Impact, 2020; nam_ua670-2_530 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ualbany Strategic Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_531 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - UG Office Grand Opening, Undated; nam_ua670-2_532 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - University Library Renovation, Undated; nam_ua670-2_533 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - University Senate, Undated; nam_ua670-2_534 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - University of Laval- Quebec, Canada, Undated; nam_ua670-2_535 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - UPC-University Planning and Policy Council, Undated; nam_ua670-2_536 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Urban Research and Outreach Engagement, Undated; nam_ua670-2_537 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - URPAC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_538 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Utica-Rome, Undated; nam_ua670-2_539 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - UUP Discretionary Raises, Undated; nam_ua670-2_540 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - UUP Salary Listing, Undated; nam_ua670-2_541 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - U.S. News, Undated; nam_ua670-2_542 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vaio-Laptop, Undated; nam_ua670-2_543 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Washington, University of, Undated; nam_ua670-2_544 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Watervliet Innovation Center, Undated; nam_ua670-2_545 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - WEB, Undated; nam_ua670-2_546 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Webmasters Guild, Undated; nam_ua670-2_547 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Wii Current, Undated; nam_ua670-2_548 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Workstudy, Undated; nam_ua670-2_549 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Women Studies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_550 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Working Groups, Undated; nam_ua670-2_551 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - WSIS, Undated; nam_ua670-2_552 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Zogby International, Undated; nam_ua670-2_553 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The IACE Application For Accreditation of Information Assurance, 2004; nam_ua670-2_554 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - College-Wide Handouts, Undated; nam_ua670-2_555 (Box 15, Item 2)
  - Advisory Workgroup, 2008; nam_ua670-2_556 (Box 15, Item 3)
  - Academic Advisory Committee, 2007; nam_ua670-2_557 (Box 15, Item 4)
  - Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program in Information Science, 2009; nam_ua670-2_558 (Box 15, Item 5)
  - Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program in Information Science, 2009; nam_ua670-2_559 (Box 15, Item 6)
  - Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program in Information Science, 2009; nam_ua670-2_560 (Box 15, Item 7)
  - Background Materials: NYS Office of Cyber Security and Infrastructure, 2007; nam_ua670-2_561 (Box 15, Item 8)
  - Background Materials: NYS Office of Cyber Security and Infrastructure, 2007; nam_ua670-2_562 (Box 15, Item 9)
  - Dean's Office: College of Computing And Information, 2012; nam_ua670-2_563 (Box 15, Item 10)
  - The Institute for Fianancial Market Regulations, Undated; nam_ua670-2_564 (Box 15, Item 11)
  - Watervliet Innovation Center, Undated; nam_ua670-2_565 (Box 15, Item 12)
  - Homeland Solutions: Training Development-Procurment, Undated; nam_ua670-2_566 (Box 15, Item 13)